A Guide to the Papers of the Tucker, Harrison and Smith Families, 1790-1940
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
- Edward Tiffin Harrison to Professor Francis H. Smith 1865 March 10, ALS (Box 15)
- General Gorgas to J. Howard Smith 1865 March 14, LS (Box 15)
- Emma G. Howard to Summerfield Smith 1865 April 1, ALS (Box 15)
- John B. Minor to William Overton 1865 April 1, ALS (Box 15)
- Mary Jane Harrison to [?] 1865 April 20, AL (fragment) (Box 15)
- John A. Broadus to Professor Francis H. Smith 1865 April 26, ALS (Box 15)
- Daniel G. Smith to Eliza Smith 1865 April 26, ALS (Box 15)
- Mary Jane Harrison to Caroline E. Harrison [1865 April], ALS (Box 15)
- George Tucker Harrison to [Professor Francis H. Smith] 1865 June 11, ALS (Box 15)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Mary Stuart Smith 1865 June 25, ALS (Box 15)
- Eleanor Rosalie Harrison Thorton to sister, Mrs. M. S. Smith 1865 June 25, ALS (Box 15)
- Eliza (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1865 July 13, & 19; Oct. 2 & 20, 4 ALS (Box 15)
- Lidie R. (Hamilton) Uhler to Eliza E. Smith 1865 Aug. 17 & Dec. 2, 2 ALS (Box 15)
- Lucy (Stevens) Clarke to [Caroline E. Harrison] 1865 Sept. 18, ALS (Box 15)
- [Mary F. Harrison] to Mary Jane Harrison 1865 Sept. 18, AL, (fragment) (Box 15)
- Edward Buckey to Daniel G. Smith (F. H. S.'s father) 1865 Nov. 18, ALS (Box 15)
- Knowles & Ealford to Professor Francis H. Smith 1865, 1 item (Box 15)
- Edward Buckey to Daniel G. Smith 1866 Feb. 20; June, 2 ALS (Box 15)
- Lidier (Hamilton) Uhler to Ellen E. Smith 18655 March 12; May 21; Aug. 8; Dec. 27, 3 ALS, 1 AL (Box 15)
- Edward B. Smith to Daniel G. Smith 1866 March 25; April 16; June 12, 14, 23; July 3, 6 ALS (Box 15)
- Savilla Lugenbul to Daniel G. Smith [1866?] March 23, ALS (Box 15)
- Francis H. Smith to [?] 1866 April 23, ALS (Box 16)
- Edward B. Smith to father 1866 May 20, ALS (Box 16)
- Eliza P. Hamilton to Ellen E. Smith 1866 May 21, ALS (Box 16)
- Sam[uel] Rodgers to [Daniel G.] Smith 1866 May 22, ALS (Box 16)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Ellen E. Smith 1866 May 30, ALS (Box 16)
- Edward B. Smith to Francis H. Smith 1866 Sept. 4 & Dec. 24, 2 ALS (Box 16)
- Professor Henry Tutwiler to Professor Francis H. Smith 1866 Sept. 24, ALS (Box 16)
- C. B. Richardson to Francis H. Smith 1866 Sept. 25, ALS (Box 16)
- George Rives to Francis H. Smith 1866 Oct. 7 [1866], ALS (Box 16)
- Williette (Stevens) Baughman to Aunt Mary Jane Harrison 1866 Dec. 7, ALS (Box 16)
- Mary F. Harrison (Mrs. P. Rush Harrison) to Mary Jane Harrison 1867 Jan. 10 & Feb. 18, 2 ALS (Box 16)
- C. B. Richardson to Francis H. Smith 1867 Jan. 14; April 25, & 26, 2 ALS, 1 printed letter (Box 16)
- Francis H. Smith to C. B. Richardson 1867 Jan. 16 & March 26, 2 ALS (copies) (Box 16)
- Edward B. Smith to brother Francis H. Smith 1867 Jan. 28, ALS (Box 16)
- Edward Buckey to Daniel G. Smith 1867 Jan. 29 & Feb. 14, 2 ALS (Box 16)
- Daniel G. Smith to Francis H. Smith 1867 Feb. 6, ALS (Box 16)
- Edward B. Smith to Francis H. Smith 1867 Feb. 21; June 1; Nov. 2, 3 ALS (Box 16)
- John C. Wallace to Caroline E. Harrison 1867 March 18, ALS (Box 16)
- Lucy Smith (Mrs. Edward B. Smith) to Daniel G. Smith 1867 March, ALS (Box 16)
- Eleanor R. Harrison Thornton to Aunt Mary S. Harrison 1867 May 3, ALS (Box 16)
- Lucy Rush Harrison to aunts [?] 1867 May 7, ALS (Box 16)
- Fannie M. Stuart (Mrs. J. C. Wallace) to Mary Jane Harrison 1867 July 9, ALS (Box 16)
- Alex. H. Stuart to [?] 1867 July 17; [1867?], ALS & draft (Box 16)
- Frank Stevens to his aunts [Carrie Harrison] and [Mary ?] 1867 July 23, AL (fragment) (Box 16)
- William Peters to Professor F. H. Smith 1867 July 29, ALS (Box 16)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1867 Aug. 31, ALS (Box 16)
- Charles C. Harrison to Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison 1867 Sept. 19, ALS (Box 16)
- H. E. Hamilton to Ellen E. (Hamilton) Smith (Mrs. James L.) 1867 Nov. 1, ALS (Box 16)
- Andrew S. Hunt to Francis H. Smith 1867 Dec. 15, ALS (Box 16)
- Mary Stuart Smith to Francis H. Smith 1868 Jan. 1, ALS (Box 16)
- Edward B. Smith to Francis H. Smith 1868 Jan. 4, 2 ALS (Box 16)
- Fannie M. Stuart (Mrs. J. C. Wallace) to Caroline E. Harrison 1868 Jan. 7, ALS (Box 16)
- E. H. Stevens to Frank Stevens 1868 Jan. 17, ALS (Box 16)
- Eliza Ridgely Uhler to [Ellen and Daniel G. Smith] 1868 Jan. 18; March 9 & 10; June 9 & 10; July 10, 4 ALS, 2 AL (Box 16)
- Francis R. Rives to George Rives 1868 Jan. 20, ALS (Box 16)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1868 Jan. 29 & Nov. 7, 2 ALS (Box 16)
- Department of Agriculture to Daniel G. Smith 1868 Jan. 30, Printed letter (Box 16)
- W. L. Buckingham to J. Howard Smith 1868 Feb. 5, ALS (Box 16)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to Aunt Mary Jane Harrison 1868 April 8, ALS (Box 16)
- Eliza (Lidie) Ridgely Uhler and Eliza P. Hamilton to [Ellen Smith] 1868 April 8, ALS (Box 16)
- Henry Tutwiler to John Broadus 1868 April 20, ALS (Box 16)
- [?] to Williette (Stevens Baughman) 1868 May 11, AL (fragment) (Box 16)
- John C. Wallace to Caroline E. Harrison 1868 May 25, ALS (Box 16)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to father-in-law, Daniel G. Smith 1868 Aug. 4, ALS (Box 16)
- Francis H. Smith to wife Mary S. Smith 1868 Aug. 13 & 21, 2 ALS (Box 16)
- Francis H. Smith to Mary Stuart Smith 1868 Aug. 27, AL (Box 16)
- H. Shaffner (sister of D. Smith) to Daniel G. Smith 1868 Sept. 6, ALS (Box 16)
- Daniel G. Smith to Mary Stuart Smith 1868 Sept. 6, ALS (Box 16)
- Minnie L. Harrison (Mrs. M. White Williamson) to Caroline E. Harrison 1868 Sept. 25, ALS (Box 16)
- Albert S. Hunt to Francis H. Smith 1868 Sept. 26, ALS (Box 16)
- James Pleasants to Francis H. Smith 1868 Oct. 14, ALS (Box 16)
- Mary Stuart Smith to Francis H. Smith ca. 1868, ALS (Box 16)
- Eliza Rigely Uhler to [Ellen and Daniel G. Smith] 1869 Jan. 11; April 26; Dec. 9, 3 ALS (Box 16)
- J. L. Cabell to Daniel G. Smith 1869 Feb. 7, ALS (Box 16)
- Minnie L. Harrison (Mrs. M. White Williamson) to Mary Jane Harrison 1869 March 20, ALS (Box 16)
- H. Shaffner to Daniel G. Smith (sister of D. Smith) 1869 May 4, ALS (Box 16)
- Lucy Rush Harrison to Miss Carrie Harrison 1869 May 18, ALS (Box 16)
- Francis H. Smith to Rev. James A. Duncan, President of Randolph-Macon College regarding an Honarary Degree 1869 July 14, ALS (Box 16)
- Ann E. T. Magill to Eulina H. Magill 1869 July 16, ALS (Box 16)
- J. S. Davis to Mary (Harrison) Smith 1869 July 31, ALS (Box 16)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to husband Francis H. Smith 1869 Aug. 20; Nov. 8 & 16, 3 ALS (Box 16)
- Francis H. Smith to wife Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith 1869 Aug. 23, 27, & 30, 3 ALS (Box 16)
- F. H. Smith to wife Mary Stuart Smith (Harrison) 1869 Aug. 31; Sept. 6 & 9, 3 ALS (Box 16)
- Lelia M. Smith to Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith 1869 Sept. 8, ALS (Box 16)
- Lucy Rush Harrison to Williette [Baughman] 1869 Oct. 23, ALS (Box 16)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1869 Oct. 23, ALS (Box 16)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter Eleanor A. Smith 1869 Nov. 10, ALS (Box 16)
- Eliza Rigely Uhler to [Ellen and Daniel G. Smith] 1870 Jan. 14; March 16; June 3; Aug. 15; Sept. 19 & Oct. 14, 5 ALS, 1 AL (fragment) (Box 16)
- Mary Jane Harrison to Williette Stevens 1870 Jan. 29, ALS (Box 16)
- Francis H. Smith to Mary Stuart Smith 1870 Feb. 20; July 18; Sept. 16, 2 ALS, 1 APC (Box 16)
- Invitation to University of Maryland Commencement 1870 March 1, 1 item (Box 16)
- Charles C. Harrison to Eliza L. C. Harrison (mother) 1870 March 7, ALS (Box 16)
- Chapman Coleman to Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith 1870 March 28, ALS (Box 16)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1870 April 30 & Oct. 10, 2 ALS (Box 16)
- Eliza P. Hamilton to [Daniel G.] Smith 1870 June 7, ALS (Box 16)
- Eleanor Rosalie (Harrison) Thornton to Aunt [Mary S. Harrison] 1870 July 28, ALS (Box 16)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband Francis H. Smith 1870 Aug. 11, 13, & 23; Sept. 24, 5 ALS (Box 16)
- Francis H. Smith to wife Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith 1870 Oct. 11, ALS (Box 16)
- H. Shaffner to Daniel G. Smith sister of D. Smith 1870 Oct. 29, ALS (Box 16)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to mother-in-law Ellen E. Smith 1870 Nov. 3, ALS (Box 16)
- Lucy Smith to father [?] 1870 Nov. 20, ALS (Box 16)
- Rev. John A. Broadus to Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith 1870 Dec. 1, ALS (Box 16)
- John Bayley to [Ellen and Daniel G.] Smith 1870 Dec. 6, 2 ALS (Box 16)
- Eleanor Rosalie (Harrison) Thornton to niece Eliza L. C. Smith 1870 Dec. 23, AL (Box 16)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Eliza L. C. Smith 1870 Dec. 24, ALS (Box 16)
- Margaret Cabell Smith to Ellie [?] [1870?], ALS (Box 16)
- Mary Stuart Smith to Eliza and Eleanor ca. 1870-1890, 5 ALS, 1 AL (Box 16)
- Eleanor Rosalie (Harrison) Thornton to niece Eleanor A. Smith (Miles) (Kent) ca. 1870, ALS (Box 16)
- Eliza Rigely Uhler to [Ellen and Daniel G. Smith] 1871 Jan. 12; April 7; Oct. 13, 3 ALS (Box 16)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1871 Jan. 19; April 26; Aug. 31, 3 ALS (Box 16)
- Eliza P. Hamilton to sister E[llen Smith?]1871 Jan. 23 & Aug. 29, 2 ALS (Box 16)
- Rossey to Ellen E. Smith 1871 Feb. 16 & April 18, 2 ALS (Box 16)
- Eleanor R. (Harrison) Thornton to Aunt Mary Jane Harrison 1871 March 15, ALS (Box 16)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Eliza L. C. Smith (granddaughter) 1871 May 29, ALS (Box 16)
- Eliza L. C. Smith to grandmother Eliza L. C. (Harrison) Smith 1871 June 4; Oct. 8; Dec. 19, 2 ALS, 1 AL (Box 16)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison 1871 July 11, ALS (Box 16)
- Francis Harrison Smith to his daughter Eleanor H. Smith 1871 [July 13]; Nov. 20; Dec. 22, 2 ALS, 1 APCS (Box 17)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Eliza T. Harrison 1871 July 25, ALS (Box 17)
- Eleanor Rosalie (Harrison) Thornton to niece Eliza L. C. Smith 1871 Aug. 18, AL (fragment) (Box 17)
- Francis H. Smith to Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith 1871 Sept. 9, ALS (Box 17)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to husband Francis H. Smith 1871 Sept. 11, ALS (Box 17)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Eliza L. C. Smith 1871 Sept. 27 & Oct. 9, 2 ALS (Box 17)
- Eleanor Rosalie Harrison (Mrs. W. M. Thornton) to niece Eleanor Smith (Mrs. C. C. Kent) 1871 Oct. 9, ALS (Box 17)
- Edward Buckley Smith to his brother 1871 Oct. 12, ALS (Box 17)
- Ellen E. (Hamilton) Smith to his brother 1871 Oct. 18, ALS (Box 17)
- Eliza Lee Smith (Walker) to father, Francis Harrison Smith 1871 Oct. 20, ALS (Box 17)
- Eliza L. C. Smith (Walker) to mother Mary Stuart Smith 1871 Oct. 26; Dec. 10, 2 ALS (Box 17)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to Eliza L. C. Smith 1871 Oct. 30, AL (Box 17)
- Mahlon D. Ogden to George Rives 1871 Nov. 5, ALS (Box 17)
- Eleanor Rosalie (Harrison) Thronton to brother Francis H. Smith 1871 Dec. 13, AL, (fragment) (Box 17)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to Aunt, Mary Jane Harrison 1872 Jan. 2, ALS (Box 17)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to daughter Eleanor A. Smith 1872 Jan. 3, AL (Box 17)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter Eleanor A. Smith 1872 Jan. 3; Nov. 28, 2 ALS (Box 17)
- Eleanor Rosalie (Harrison) Thornton to Aunt Mary Jane Harrison 1872 Jan. 18, AL (Box 17)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison (sister-in-law) 1872 Jan. 22, ALS (Box 17)
- James Pleasants to Francis H. Smith 1872 Jan. 26, ALS (Box 17)
- Eliza L. C. Smith (Walker) to mother Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith 1872 Jan. 28; Feb. 9; March 29; April 18; May 11, 2 ALS, 3 AL (fragments) (Box 17)
- Daniel G. Smith to Eliza and Ellie Smith 1872 Jan., ALS (Box 17)
- Victoria Howard to her Aunt 1872 Feb. 6, ALS (Box 17)
- Eliza L. C. Smith Walker to brother Gessner Harrison Smith 1872 March & May 29, 2 ALS (Box 17)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1872 March 12, ALS (Box 17)
- Eleanor R. Harrison Thornton to aunt Mary S. Harrison 1872 March 12, ALS (Box 17)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Stuart Smith 1872 March 13; April 24; Nov. 15, 2 ALS, 1 AL(fragment) (Box 17)
- Eliza Ridgely Uhler to relatives 1872 March 16 & Aug. 19, 2 ALS (Box 17)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to Eliza L. C. Smith 1872 March 20 & May 20, 2 ALS (Box 17)
- Eliza L. C. Smith to grandmother Mrs. E. L. C. Harrison Smith 1872 March 31, ALS (Box 17)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Mary Stuart Smith 1872 April 3; Nov. 7 & 8, 3 ALS (Box 17)
- Eleanor R. Harrison Thornton to niece Eleanor A. Smith (Miles) (Kent) 1872 April 5, ALS (Box 17)
- Lelia M. Smith to Ellen Smith 1872 April 9; May 12; June 9, 3 ALS (Box 17)
- N. H. Massie to Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison 1872 April 20, ALS (Box 17)
- Eleanor Rosaile Harrison Thornton to niece Eliza L. C. Smith 1872 April 23, ALS (Box 17)
- Gessner Harrison Smith to sister 1872 April, ALS (Box 17)
- Daniel G. Smith to Mary Stuart Smith 1872 May 20, ALS (Box 17)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Eleanor A. (Ellie) Smith 1872 May 28 & 31; June 7; Dec. 24, 4 ALS (Box 17)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1872 June 18; Dec. 19, 2 ALS (Box 17)
- Mary Stuart to Eliza L. C. (Smith) Walker [1872?] June 18, AL (Box 17)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Eliza L. C. Smith 1872 June 20, ALS (Box 17)
- George Rives to Mary Stuart Smith 1872 June 27, ALS (Box 17)
- Matthew Fontaine Maury and C. M. Polton to Professor Francis H. Smith, University of Virginia 1872 Aug. 7; 21, 23, & 29, 4 ALS (Box 17)
- C. M. Bolton to Francis H. Smith 1872 Aug. 15, ALS (Box 17)
- C. M. Bolton and [Francis H. Smith?] to Colonel H. D. Whitcomb 1872 Oct. 16 & 17, 2 ALS (Box 17)
- John Bayley to Ellen E. (Hamilton) Smith 1872 Oct. 29, ALS (Box 17)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Smith 1872 Dec. 26, ALS (Box 17)
- Ellen E. (Hamilton) Smith to Eliza and Ellie (Smith) (grandchildren) ca. 1872, ALS (Box 17)
- Eliza Ridgely Uhler to Ellen [E. Smith] 1873 Jan. 1; Feb. 6; June 27, 3 ALS (Box 17)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Eliza Lewis Smith (daughter of Mary Stuart Smith) 1873 Jan. 2, ALS (Box 17)
- Frank Stevens to his aunts Carrie and Mary [Harrison] 1873 March 15; May 9; Dec. 6, ALS (Box 17)
- Williette (Stevens) Baughman to Aunt Caroline and Mary Jane Harrison 1873 April 3; June 15; June, ALS (Box 17)
- Maria F. (Tucker) Rives to Mary Stuart Smith 1873 April 13, ALS (Box 17)
- Edward T. Harrison to Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith 1873 May 7; Nov. 10, ALS (Box 17)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) to Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Smith 1873 May 11; Sept. 7, & 8; Oct. 7 & Dec. 1, 4 ALS, 1 AL (Box 17)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Stuart Smith 1873 May 13; June 9; July 22; Aug. 9 & 16; Nov. 11; Dec. 10 & 30, 8 ALS (Box 17)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to Aunt Mary Jane Harrison 1873 May 18, ALS (Box 17)
- John A. Broadus to Professor Francis H. Smith 1873 May 23, ALS (Box 17)
- Eliza L. C. (Smith) Walker to mother Mary Stuart Smith 1873 May 23 & 29; June 9; Sept. 23; Oct. 8; Dec., 5 ALS, AL (Box 17)
- Mary W. Ross to Ellen E. (Hamilton) Smith 1873 May 27, ALS (Box 17)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1873 June 13; Aug. 7; Nov. 7, 3 ALS (Box 17)
- John A. Broadus to Francis H. Smith 1873 June 25, ALS (Box 17)
- J. L. Cabell to Francis H. Smith 1873 June 25, ALS (Box 17)
- Rev. John A. Broadus to Professor F. H. Smith 1873 June 27; Dec. 8 & 15, 3 ALS (Box 17)
- George C. Rives to Francis H. Smith 1873 July 12, ALS (Box 17)
- Daniel G. Smith to [?] 1873 July 14, ALS (Box 17)
- John Bayley to [Francis H. Smith 1873 July 23, ALS (Box 17)
- Mrs. John L. Cabell to Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison 1873 Aug. 4, ALS (Box 17)
- A. G. Haygood to Mary Stuart Smith 1873 Aug. 4, ALS (Box 17)
- John Bayley to Mary Stuart Smith 1873 Aug. 11, ALS (Box 17)
- J. C. Granbery to Mary Stuart Smith 1873 Aug. 12, ALS (Box 17)
- Henry William Harrison to Mary Stuart Smith 1873 Aug. 25, ALS (Box 17)
- Gessner Harrison Smith to Edward Tiffin Harrison 1873 Oct. 8, ALS (Box 17)
- Mary Jane Harrison to Williette (Stevens) Baugham 1873 Oct. 13, ALS (Box 17)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to brother Edward T. Harrison [1873] Oct. 24, ALS (Box 17)
- John A. Broadus to Francis H. Smith 1873 Oct. 28, ALS (Box 17)
- Dr. C. Fayette Taylor to [Mary Stuart] Smith 1875 Oct. 29, ALS (Box 17)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to mother Eliza L. C. Harrison 1873 Dec. 2, ALS (Box 17)
- Waller Holladay to G. T. Harrison 1873 Dec. 3, ALS (Box 17)
- Eliza L. C. Smith to grandmother Eliza L. C. Harrison 1873 Dec. 3, ALS (Box 17)
- Eleanor Rosalie Harrison Thornton to brother F. H. Smith 1873 Dec. 3, ALS (Box 17)
- Francis H. Smith to Mrs. (Gessner) Harrison 1873 Dec. 30, ALS (Box 17)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Francis H. Smith 1874 Jan. 1, ALS (Box 18)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison 1874 Jan. 8; Feb. 10 & 17; March 20 & 31; April 4 & 28; June 25 & Oct. 3, 9 ALS (Box 18)
- Frank Stevens to Carrie E. Harrison 1874 Jan. 9; Nov. 21; Dec. 14, 3 ALS (Box 18)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Stuart Smith 1874 Jan. 10; June 25; June 26, July 31, 4 ALS (Box 18)
- Williette (Stevens) Baughman to Aunt Caroline Harrison 1874 Jan. 17; July 15, 2 ALS (Box 18)
- C. C. Boughman to Caroline E. Harrison 1874 Jan. 18, ALS (Box 18)
- Eliza L. C. Smith to grandmother Eliza L. C. Harrison 1874 Jan. 29, ALS (Box 18)
- Peachey G. Harrison to Mrs. Mary Stuart Smith [sister] 1874 Jan. 30, ALS (Box 18)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1874 Feb. 12 & March 6, 2 ALS (Box 18)
- J. L. Hamilton to his sister 1874 Feb. 20, ALS (Box 18)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Mary Stuart Smith 1874 Feb. 21, ALS (Box 18)
- Mary Jane Harrison to Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison 1874 Feb. 24, ALS (Box 18)
- Daniel G. Smith to Mary Stuart Smith 1874 March 7, ALS (Box 18)
- Rev. John A. Broadus to Professor F. H. Smith 1874 March 7; Nov. 12; Dec. 10, 3 ALS (Box 18)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband F. H. Smith 1874 May 4; July 16, 2 ALS (Box 18)
- Eliza Ridgely Uhler to Daniel G. and Ellen E. Smith 1874 May 9; Oct. 19; Dec. 31, 3 ALS (Box 18)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1874 June 16 & July 30, 2 ALS (Box 18)
- Francis H. Smith to wife Mary S. Smith 1874 July 17 & 18; [ ca. July 24]; Sept. 1, 2 AL, 2 APC (Box 18)
- Albert S. Hunt to Francis H. Smith 1874 July 20, ALS (Box 18)
- Robert Lewis Harrison to sister, Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith 1874 July 25, ALS (Box 18)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband F. H. Smith 1874 July 25, 2 ALS, 2 APC, 1 AL (Box 18)
- Eliza L. C. Smith to sister Eleanor A. Smith 1874 July 28 & Nov. 10, 2 ALS (Box 18)
- Eliza P. Hamilton to sister E[llen Smith]1874 July 29, ALS (Box 18)
- Gessner Harrison Smith to Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison (grandmother) 1874 Aug. 9, ALS (Box 18)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to [Aunt Mary Jane Harrison] 1874 Aug. 13, 2 ALS (Box 18)
- John A. Broadus to Mary Stuart Smith (his sister-in-law) 1874 Aug. 14, ALS (Box 18)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to G. Harrison Smith 1874 Aug. 14, 2 ALS (Box 18)
- Peachey G. Harrison to Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison 1874 Aug. 16, ALS (Box 18)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to Eliza L. C. Smith 1874 Aug. 29, AL (Box 18)
- Henry William Harrison to sister Mrs. Francis H. Smith 1874 Aug. 25, ALS (Box 18)
- Mary Jane Harrison to Mary Stuart Smith 1874 Aug., ALS (Box 18)
- Sallie Rives (Mrs. George C. Rives) to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1874 Sept. 14, ALS (Box 18)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Mary Jane Harrison 1874 Sept. 16, ALS (Box 18)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to Aunt, Mary Jane Harrison 1874 Nov. 19, ALS (Box 18)
- Williette (Stevens) Baughman to aunt, [Mary Jane Harrison?] 1874 Nov. 30, ALS (Box 18)
- Fannie M. Stuart (Mrs. J. C. Wallace) to Caroline E. Harrison 1874 Dec. 28, ALS (Box 18)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Stuart Smith 1875 Jan. 14; June 18; Sept. 27, 3 ALS (Box 18)
- J. Howard Smith to Colonel F. G. Ruffin 1875 Jan. 20, ALS (Box 18)
- Eliza Ridgely Uhler to Ellen E. and Daniel G. Smith 1875 Jan. 20 & Dec. 13, 2 ALS (Box 18)
- H. Potts to J. Howard Smith 1875 Feb. 5 & March 28, 2 ALS (Box 18)
- J. R. Bryan, Jr. to J. Howard Smith 1875 April 5, ALS (Box 18)
- Daniel G. Smith to Mary Stuart Smith 1875 April 5, ALS (Box 18)
- Marie B. B. to Williette (Stevens) Baughman 1875 July 22, ALS (Box 18)
- Rev. John A. Broadus to Mrs. Mary S. Smith 1875 Aug. 2, ALS (Box 18)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband F. H. Smith 1875 Aug. 10; Sept. 5-28, 3 ALS, 7 APCS (Box 18)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1875 Aug. 23, ALS (Box 18)
- Lucy Rush Harrison to her Aunt Carrie 1875 Dec. 3, ALS (Box 18)
- J. S. Smith to J. Howard Smith [1875?], ALS (Box 18)
- Mary Stuart Smith to Eliza L. C. Harrison [ ca. 1875], ALS (Box 18)
- Lucy R. Harrison to Miss C. E. Harrison 1876 Jan. 11; April 7; July 4; Oct. 3, 4 ALS (Box 18)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Eliza L. C. Smith 1876 Jan. 21, ALS (Box 18)
- Edward Buckley Smith to his father 1876 Feb. 19, ALS (Box 18)
- Eliza Ridgely Uhler to [Ellen and Daniel G. Smith] 1876 March 3, ALS (Box 18)
- Lucy Rush Harrison to Williette [Stevens Baughman] 1876 May 4, ALS (Box 18)
- Edward Buckey to Francis H. Smith 1876 May 31, ALS (Box 18)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Mary [?] 1876 July 5; Nov. 27, 2 ALS (Box 18)
- Eliza L. C. Smith (Walker) to father, Francis H. Smith 1876 July 31; Dec. 16 & 24, 1 ALS, 1 AL, 1 APCS, 1 APC (Box 18)
- [?] to Williette (Stevens) Baughman 1876 Oct. 9, AL, (fragment) (Box 18)
- Minnie L. Harrison (Mrs. M. White Williamson) to aunt [Caroline E. Harrison] 1876 Oct. 14 & 15, 2 ALS (Box 18)
- Francis H. Smith to Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith 1876 Oct. 25, ALS (Box 18)
- Minnie L. Harrison (Mrs. M. White Williamson) to Mary Jane Harrison 1876 Nov. 8, ALS (Box 18)
- Mira Harrison to cousin [Caroline Harrison] 1876 Nov. 8, ALS (Box 18)
- Albert S. Hunt to Francis H. Smith 1876 Nov. 9, ALS (Box 18)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Eliza L. C. Smith 1877 Jan. 3, ALS (Box 18)
- Minnie L. Harrison (Mrs. M. White Williamson) to aunt Caroline E. Harrison 1877 June 5, ALS (Box 18)
- Eliza L. C. [Smith] Walker to sister, Ellie A. (Smith) Kent 1877 Jan. 10 & Nov. 26, 2 ALS (Box 18)
- Mary Jane Harrison to Mary Stuart Smith 1877 April 2, ALS (Box 18)
- Eliza Ridgely Uhler to [Ellen and Daniel Smith] 1877 April 25, ALS (Box 18)
- Rev. John A. Broadus to Mrs. Mary S. Smith 1877 May 2, AL (Box 18)
- Lucy R. Harrison to C. E. Harrison 1877 May 5, ALS (Box 18)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison 1877 May 21, ALS (Box 18)
- Laura V. Getzendaner to Professor Francis H. Smith 1877 July 24, ALS (Box 18)
- Francis H. Smith to his wife, Mary S. Smith 1877 Aug. 21, ALS (Box 18)
- Fannie M. Stuart (Mrs. C. C. Wallace) to Caroline E. Harrison 1877 Sept. 6, ALS (Box 18)
- Eliza L. C. Smith to grandmother, Mrs. E. L. C. (Tucker) Harrison 1877 Sept. 25 & Dec. 20, 2 ALS (Box 18)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Stuart Smith (daughter) 1877 Oct. 2, ALS (Box 18)
- Wyatt Eaton to Lelia M. Smith 1877 Oct. 16, ALS (Box 18)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Lelia M. Smith 1877 Oct. 24, ALS (Box 18)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Eliza Tucker Harrison 1877 Oct. 24, ALS (Box 18)
- Eunice Rogers to Mrs. Harrison 1877 Nov. 6, ALS (Box 18)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1877 Nov. 8, ALS (Box 18)
- Daniel G. Smith to Ellie Smith 1877 Nov. 10, ALS (Box 18)
- Williette (Stevens) Baughman to aunt, Caroline E. Harrison 1877 Nov. 17, ALS (Box 18)
- Frank Stevens to his Aunt Mary 1877 Dec. 3, ALS (Box 18)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Stuart Smith 1877 Dec. 4, 4 ALS (Box 18)
- Eliza P. Hamilton to Ellen E. (Hamilton) Smith 1877 Dec. 5, ALS (Box 18)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Eleanor (Ellie) Smith 1877 Dec. 14, ALS (Box 18)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to daughter Lelia M. Smith (Mrs. Lucian Cocke) 1877 Dec. 15, ALS (Box 18)
- E. L. C. (Smith) Walker to mother, Mary Stuart Smith 1878 Jan. 4; Feb. 10 & 24; March 8; June 2, 4 ALS, 1 AL (Box 19)
- Minnie L. Harrison (Mrs. M. White Williamson) to aunt, Caroline E. Harrison 1878 Jan. 7; Dec. 18, ALS, APCS (Box 19)